christiesgreatestates.com 2013-04-20

# Privacy Policy | Christie's International Real Estate

**Personal Data Privacy and Protection Policy**

Christie's International Real Estate, Inc. and Christie’s International Real Estate Limited (together, the “Company”, “Christie’s International Real Estate”, “we” or “us”) consider the privacy and protection of our clients' personal data to be of utmost importance. To ensure that you feel confident about providing us with your personal information when communicating with us and using our services, our practices in relation to the collection and use of personal data are outlined below.

 **Purposes**  
We will collect, record, store, and use your personal data worldwide but only to enable you to purchase or sell real property through the affiliates of Christie's International Real Estate and unless you object, to advise you of services to market or to purchase real property.

**Privacy**  
We will not share your personal data with anyone outside the Christie's International Plc group of companies without your consent.

From time to time, however, we may need to disclose your personal data to sales associates and/or officers of designated affiliates of Christie’s International Real Estate or to contractors of Christie's International Real Estate in order to enable us to communicate with you or to customize the Web Site to better serve you. These persons are required to keep the information confidential and will not use the information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Christie's International Real Estate. 

**Security**  
Any personal data you provide to us is securely stored in a database held by Christie's International Real Estate, Inc. in New Mexico, Illinois, and New York—to which only authorized Christie's International Real Estate employees and agents have access.

We have put in place administrative measures to ensure that the access that Christie's International Real Estate employees and agents have to personal data on our server is limited to the extent necessary in order to perform their functions.

All our employees are required to sign a confidentiality agreement in which they agree to treat personal data as strictly confidential.

The server holding your personal data is protected against both unauthorized physical and electronic access. These measures include an electronic firewall and various other protection measures that involve virus scanning, installation of security patches, vulnerability testing, backup and recovery planning, employee training, security audits, and other steps designed to constantly improve the data protection posture. The server is not directly connected to the Internet, and therefore data is available only to authorized computers.

While we strive to provide security that is above and beyond industry standards, because of the Internet’s inherent vulnerabilities, we cannot ensure or warrant complete security of all information transmitted to us. 

**Christie's International Real Estate and the Internet**

 **Web Site**  
In general, you may browse our Internet site anonymously. However, some of our online services require the collection of some personally identifying information, such as your name, address, and, when appropriate, your credit information.

For transactions over the Christie's International Real Estate web site that involve particularly sensitive information, such as credit card numbers and accounting information, we will employ accepted transmission and storage protocols, such as encryption, to prevent this information from being disclosed. This means that when you type in sensitive information, such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into codes before being securely sent to us over the Internet.

This information will be used for processing transactions, but it may also be used for internal data processing, such as compiling statistical information about your interests and the use of our Internet site. As a service to you, we may also use this information to customize the content we offer.

 **Email**  
In order to provide you with timely notice regarding new real property offered for sale, Christie's International Real Estate may send you email notices. To facilitate this service, we may note some of the pages you visit on our Web site.

At any time, you may discontinue this service by sending an email to [info@christiesrealestate.com](mailto:info@christiesrealestate.com) and requesting that your email address be removed from our lists.

 **Business Relationships**  
The Christie's International Real Estate sites contain links to other Web sites. None of the information that you provide to us will be transmitted to other Web sites. Christie's International Real Estate is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Cookies**  
Christie's International Real Estate may also use on its Internet properties a personalization technology called a "cookie." A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer's hard disk that identifies your browser software to a Web site. Cookies allow us to track when you enter, leave, and re-enter our sites and what path you take through our sites. In doing this, we can provide you with a more personalized experience.

 **Finding Luxury Estates for Sale**  
Christie's International Real Estate provides users of this site the opportunity to receive information about real property offered for sale, which will require Christie’s International Real Estate to provide your email address(es) to our affiliate brokers.

If you do not wish to receive further email from the sender, please reply to the sender and request that they stop sending you such emails in the future. Christie's International Real Estate does not accept responsibility for any third party's use (or misuse) of this service.

 **Exceptions**  
While we will not voluntarily disclose your personal data, we may disclose such information if we are required to do so by a court order, if we are requested to do so by government or law enforcement authorities, if we are required to do so pursuant to other legal processes, or if it becomes necessary to protect the rights or property of Christie's International Real Estate, Inc.

 **Contact**  
If you have any queries in relation to the use and protection of your personal data, please contact us at  [info@christiesrealestate.com](mailto:info@christiesrealestate.com).

**Your Security Is Important to Us**

An increasingly common scam—called "phishing"—uses official-looking emails to deceive consumers into disclosing their personal information. The email often directs the recipient to a "look-alike" Web site of a legitimate business, tricking consumers into thinking they are responding to a valid request.

To avoid getting caught in any of these scams, please remember to:

  * Keep your password secret and change it periodically.
  * Never give out your vital account information by email or telephone, unless you initiated the contact. **Christie's International Real Estate never sends emails asking for personal information.**
  * Whenever you wish to register at christiesrealestate.net, edit or add new information to your account, or set up a new Christie's International Real Estate, Inc. account, please make sure the URL address is as follows: http://www.christiesrealestate.net. You may want to add this URL to your browser's Favorites or Bookmarks menu.
  * Always end your secure session on the Internet completely by clicking the “Log Out” link and by closing your browser's window before you leave the computer.
